[{
    "question": "How old is Dr.Kureha ?",
    "choice1": "139 yo",
    "choice2": "140 yo",
    "choice3": "141 yo",
    "choice4": "I don't know",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "What was Dr.Hiluluk's research about ?",
    "choice1": "A medecine capable of curing all diseases",
    "choice2": "A cherry tree seed that can germinate in snowy terrain",
    "choice3": "A substance that colors snowflakes pink",
    "choice4": "A remedy for amiudake",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    "question": "Under which eye is Luffy's scar located ?",
    "choice1": "To the right",
    "choice2": "To the left",
    "choice3": "It is a secret",
    "choice4": "I don't know where is my left and right",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question": "How much does Ussop's hammer weight ?",
    "choice1": "1kg",
    "choice2": "10kg",
    "choice3": "1t",
    "choice4": "5t",
    "answer": 4
},
{
    "question": "Which of Chopper's horn is broken ?",
    "choice1": "The right one",
    "choice2": "The left one",
    "choice3": "Both",
    "choice4": "None",
    "answer": 4
},
{
    "question": "What does Mr.3 likes to drink ?",
    "choice1": "Coffee",
    "choice2": "Milk",
    "choice3": "Tea",
    "choice4": "Sake",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "Who sucks all of the poison out of Luffy's body ?",
    "choice1": "Hancock",
    "choice2": "Reiju",
    "choice3": "Nami",
    "choice4": "Robin",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question": "Who was the first marine Admiral to be shown in the series ?",
    "choice1": "Akainu",
    "choice2": "Aokiji",
    "choice3": "Kizaru",
    "choice4": "Sengoku",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question": "Who was the first villain to defeat Luffy ?",
    "choice1": "Don Krieg",
    "choice2": "Aarlong",
    "choice3": "Baggy",
    "choice4": "Crocodile",
    "answer": 4
},
{
    "question": "Who is the first man to have joined Gol D.Roger's crew ?",
    "choice1": "Buggy The Star Clown",
    "choice2": "Red-Haired Shanks",
    "choice3": "Silver Rayleigh",
    "choice4": "Crocus",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "Where was Gol D.Roger executed ?",
    "choice1": "Raftel",
    "choice2": "Loguetown",
    "choice3": "Goa Kingdom",
    "choice4": "Gray Terminal",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question": "Who was the first Warlord of the sea to be introduced ?",
    "choice1": "Dracula Mihawk",
    "choice2": "Jimbei",
    "choice3": "Crocodile",
    "choice4": "Blackbeard",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    "question": "How many times did Zoro lose to Kuina ?",
    "choice1": "101",
    "choice2": "201",
    "choice3": "2001",
    "choice4": "1001",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "Which sword does Zoro use with his mouth ?",
    "choice1": "Wado Ichimonji",
    "choice2": "Shusui",
    "choice3": "Sandai Kitetsu",
    "choice4": "Enma",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    "question": "What is the name of Brook's old crew ?",
    "choice1": "The Roshio Pirates",
    "choice2": "The On-Air Pirates",
    "choice3": "The Rumbar Pirates",
    "choice4": "The Spade Pirates",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "Which weapon did Uso... Sogeking use to shoot the World Government flag in Enies Lobby ?",
    "choice1": "Ginga Pachinko",
    "choice2": "Kuro Kabuto",
    "choice3": "Kabuto",
    "choice4": "A bazooka",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "How many members are there in the Worst Generation ?",
    "choice1": "10",
    "choice2": "11",
    "choice3": "13",
    "choice4": "12",
    "answer": 4
},
{
    "question": "What is the name of Kizaru's fruit ?",
    "choice1": "Glint-Glint Fruit",
    "choice2": "Light-Light Fruit",
    "choice3": "Glow-Glow Fruit",
    "choice4": "Gleam-Gleam Fruit",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    "question": "Why exactly does Se√±or Pink wear baby clothes ?",
    "choice1": "Because his baby dies",
    "choice2": "Because it made his wife smile",
    "choice3": "Because he genuinely finds it fashionable",
    "choice4": "Because it's hard-boiled",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question": "Where was the first Road Poneglyph located taht the Straw Hats found ?",
    "choice1": "Fishman Island",
    "choice2": "Zou",
    "choice3": "Wholecake Island",
    "choice4": "Wano",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question": "Who could not only listen, but communicate with Zunesha ?",
    "choice1": "Momonosuke",
    "choice2": "Luffy",
    "choice3": "Inuarashi",
    "choice4": "Nekomamushi",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    "question": "What is the only race/tribe you can't find on Tottoland ?",
    "choice1": "Mink Tribe",
    "choice2": "Three-Eye Tribe",
    "choice3": "Merfolk",
    "choice4": "Giants",
    "answer": 4
},
{
    "question": "Who is the first Straw Hat to be shown in the anime ?",
    "choice1": "Luffy",
    "choice2": "Nami",
    "choice3": "Zoro",
    "choice4": "Usopp",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question": "Which of Usopp's lies ultimately turns out to be true ?",
    "choice1": "The 8,000 men under his command",
    "choice2": "The doormat monster",
    "choice3": "Giant fish dropping droppings the size of an island",
    "choice4": "None of these lies turn out to be true",
    "answer": 3
}]